sensoro.com 2017-06-10

# SENSORO

### Privacy Policy

Sensoro Inc. ("Sensoro") is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers, and seeks to provide a safe and secure customer experience. Sensoro will use its best efforts to ensure that the information submitted or gathered remains private, and is only used for the purposes set forth herein.

By purchasing or using the Sensoro Website or Sensoro Products, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Policy. Please read the Policy carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information, please do not use the Sensoro Website and Sensoro Products.

1DEFINITIONS

"Sensoro Website(s)" or "Website(s)" mean any websites, web pages, and any subpages under Sensoro's control. This also includes the contents of the Websites, which includes but is not limited to text, images, audio content, videos, designs, graphics, information, logos, downloadable content, software, and any other content found on the Websites.

"Sensoro Product(s)" means and refers to any products purchased from Sensoro or through the Sensoro Websites."

"You", "Your", and "Customer" mean and refer to all individuals and/or entities who are accessing or using the Websites or Sensoro Products for any reason.

2SCOPE

This Policy applies to the Website and Sensoro Products. This Policy regulates the processing of information relating to you. The Website may contain links to other websites over which we have no control. Sensoro is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such other websites. We also do not control the data use practices of employers and third-party advertising networks.

3INFORMATION COLLECTED

Personal Information. Sensoro collects general information about all of our Customers in aggregate when they use the Website. Most of the information collected during the purchase and ordering process will be used to process orders. If You make purchases through the Website for Sensoro Products, we do collect personal information provided to us. The personal information includes, but is not limited to, Your name, address, email, account number, and other contact information. We also may acquire personal information from third parties who provide it to us.

Behavioral Information. Sensoro may collect behavioral information regarding how You use the Website. This includes, but is not limited to, Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, location, browser, access times, operating system, and referring website addresses. This information is used to analyze the use of resources, prevent fraud, troubleshoot, and also improve our services. Sensoro also may acquire behavioral information from third parties who provide it to us. Sensoro may also personalize the advertising shown to You on the Websites, based on the information provided and collected.

4USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

Use by Sensoro. Sensoro does not disclose personal information or other information related to Your visit to the Website to any third parties except as provided in this Policy. We use the information collected through the Website for responding to any inquiries, operating and improving the Website, creating a positive Customer experience. The information gathered and collected on the Website may be shared internally at Sensoro to deliver its products and services.

By using the Website, You have consented for us to use Your information to: (1) analyze the use of resources, prevent fraud, troubleshoot, improve our products and services, and develop new products and services; (2) personalize the advertising shown to You on the Websites; (3) contact You about Sensoro Products and other updates; (4) provide You with additional information and promotions; (5) enable You to provide feedback and for us to respond to the feedback; (6) conduct surveys, promotions, and contests, and provide the results thereof; and (7) generate internal reports.

Disclosure to Third Parties. We may share Your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of Sensoro Products and other services. Sensoro may also disclose information to third parties employed by Sensoro to perform functions on our behalf. We may also disclose information to third parties if You consent to such disclosure. We may also share aggregate anonymous information about visitors to the Website to various third parties. Sensoro discloses information, if legally required to do so, or at our request pursuant to a request from a governmental entity. We may also disclose information if we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect Your safety, protect the safety of others, or investigate fraud.

Successors. We may disclose and/or transfer any information to a third party who acquires any or all of Sensoro’s business and business units, whether such acquisition is by merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a substantial portion of Sensoro’s assets. In addition, in the event Sensoro becomes the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Sensoro or its liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.

5ONLINE PAYMENTS

If You place any orders or make any payments online through the Websites, Your payment information will be and is protected by encryption, such as with the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. The SSL protocol makes it difficult for Your payment information to be stolen or intercepted during transmission.)

6CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Updates. If Sensoro makes a substantial and material change or update to the substance of this Policy, Sensoro will post a prominent notice of such change, together with a link to the revised Policy, on the Website. It is Your responsibility to review the current Policy and, if you disagree with any of the terms of the Policy, you should (i) discontinue Your use of the Website and/or Sensoro’s Products and/or (ii) inform Sensoro via the contact us link at the end of this Policy.

Contact Information. Your information, documents, and other data are submitted to Sensoro’s servers. These servers are situated in the QingCloud and maintained by Sensoro, whose principal place of business is 2807#, B, T1, WangJing SOHO, ChaoYang, Beijing 100020. If You have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or believe that they have not been adhered to, please contact Sensoro at this address. Sensoro will use reasonable efforts to answer any questions and resolve any problems.

7MISCELLANEOUS

Cookies. A cookie is a small text file stored, often temporarily, on Your computer's memory or placed on Your hard drive by a Webpage server. Cookies allow Sensoro to retrieve the information previously provided, so that You can easily use the features that You customized. Cookies allow for faster, more accurate, and more personalized results. Sensoro may use cookies, both session and persistent, to help personalize and maximize Your experience in using the Website. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies at any time by modifying Your Internet browser settings. We have no access or control over third-party cookies.

Page Tags and Web Beacons. The Website may utilize electronic images called page tags (or web beacons, clear gifs, action tags, single-pixel gifts) that allow Sensoro to collect webpage usage information. These page tags are not used to access or collect personal information, but rather to inform us what content is effective. Page tags are techniques to compile aggregate statistics about webpage usage to improve the effectiveness of our services and advertisements. The information collected by the page tags may be shared with third parties for processing, so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the websites and how those visitors use the webpages. Page tags may be rendered ineffective by changing the cookie setup options in your Internet browser.

JavaScript. JavaScript is a script or programming language that enhances the functionality of websites, often for pictures. Sensoro does not collect personal data via Javascript, and it can be deactivated via the Customer's Internet browser settings.

Headings. Headings provided in this Policy are included for reference purposes only and are not to be given any substantive effect.

Effective Date. This Policy became effective as of [Jun 1], 2014 and may be revised by Sensoro from time to time.
